<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>huyendoesstuff</title>
 <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/"/>
 <updated>2025-07-26T20:02:36+00:00</updated>
 <id>huyendoesstuff.github.io</id>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Feeling good 🥰</title>
   <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/feel-good/"/>
   <updated>2025-07-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/feel-good</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A series of images either I found on the internet or in my life that make me smile.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is this cutie patootie…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/houseplants/comments/1m9w8yw/i_gave_my_princess_what_she_deserves/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../assets/images/peace_lilies.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/houseplants/comments/1m9w8yw/i_gave_my_princess_what_she_deserves/&quot;&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;style type=&quot;text/css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;&gt;
@import url('/assets/css/books.css');
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../assets/images/FGcontent1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tweet&quot; width=&quot;75%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been lucky enough to be able to share this with my parents and they get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../assets/images/FGcontent2.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No further description!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Unfinished In-between</title>
   <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/the-unfinished-in-between/"/>
   <updated>2023-04-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/the-unfinished-in-between</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My story is paced in a notebook,&lt;br /&gt;
filled with unfinished, written, blank pages,&lt;br /&gt;
torn at the crease, screaming&lt;br /&gt;
to be different.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I try to fit you in between the pages,&lt;br /&gt;
as your sharp edge deepens the old wound&lt;br /&gt;
and tears my scars anew.&lt;br /&gt;
You said sorry, but that didn’t stop the edge from cutting,&lt;br /&gt;
the skin from bleeding,&lt;br /&gt;
the heart from hurting.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The word ‘sorry’ coming out of your mouth,&lt;br /&gt;
natural as a reflex,&lt;br /&gt;
has shielded you from guilt one moment to the next,&lt;br /&gt;
now an empty nothing once sweet. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps it was you who depleted every ounce of its meaning &lt;br /&gt;
one too many times.&lt;br /&gt;
A hollow shell of broken intentions&lt;br /&gt;
fell silently on my page,&lt;br /&gt;
putting an end to our undone story.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Again</title>
   <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/again/"/>
   <updated>2022-10-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/again</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Baby girl, you’re gonna love again&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
This time, it will be better than the last&lt;br /&gt;
The shattered dreams, the broken pieces from the past&lt;br /&gt;
Will be tender, and filled with love again&lt;br /&gt;
The unnamed promises, hopeless romance&lt;br /&gt;
Will be replaced by the warm presence of the heart&lt;br /&gt;
and of the voice that says “I’m here.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My sweet, I once had this fear&lt;br /&gt;
Of being an unlovable driftwood&lt;br /&gt;
Holding on to any shore,&lt;br /&gt;
calling it home,&lt;br /&gt;
giving it my heart&lt;br /&gt;
Time and time again&lt;br /&gt;
Hope fades away, &lt;br /&gt;
with rain and tears,&lt;br /&gt;
with wind and shivers and hurts&lt;br /&gt;
Then comes one day&lt;br /&gt;
Autumn breeze tells me&lt;br /&gt;
“Baby girl, you’re gonna love again.”&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind (2004)</title>
   <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/eternal-sunshine/"/>
   <updated>2021-12-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/eternal-sunshine</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I just watched “Eternal Sunshine” for the second time. I feel differently about the movie this time. Surprisingly I like this frame:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../assets/images/eternal-sunshine-2.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having someone with whom you once felt so happy you could die being erased from your memory seems like a relief at first and unbearable once you realize how many happy memories are actually leaving you. It hurts me to see how Joel hurts Clem; assumptions building up to judgments eventually kill the image of the other person in your mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the scenes I like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The scene with two kids: Baby girl in pink cow boy hat held baby Joel’s hand and walked him out away from the bullying kids. Then they went home, with baby Joel placing a pillow on the baby girl’s face in front of the house. Baby Joel’s mom saw them, both of them waved at her: We’re just playin’! It’s such a sweet scene.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The scene at the end of the erasing procedure, with the beach house:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;What if you’d stay this time? &lt;br /&gt;Come back and make up a goodbye, at least. &lt;br /&gt; Let’s pretend we had one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s pretend we had one. Shall we? Gosh, how much I cried on this line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joel told Clem that he was scared, that’s why he walked out the door. She didn’t know he was scared. He thought she knew that about him. It seems to me that this is the first time they were vulnerable with each other, and it happens to be at the end of their story, or at least the end of his memory about her that he wanted to erase. I noticed there is this one scene when Joel admitted to Clem that he was scared, he had a genuine, relieved, beautiful smile:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../assets/images/eternal-sunshine-1.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a long time, I have had this habit in my head: Memories passing by, as if I’m on the train and I see them from the window, one after the other, or they’re on the train, and I’m at the station watching them go by. Either way, they’re passing right before my eyes. I see that exact kind of motion in “Eternal Sunshine,” which is interesting to have your imagination actualized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I realized I resisted the urge to fix these characters; I didn’t want to change them. They just happened to be that way…&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Would you lie to me?</title>
   <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/would-you-lie-to-me/"/>
   <updated>2021-12-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/would-you-lie-to-me</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Would you lie to me?&lt;br /&gt;
Pretending that you care&lt;br /&gt;
When I’m awfully lonely&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would you lie to me?&lt;br /&gt;
Pretending that you’re there&lt;br /&gt;
When I’m facing my worst fear&lt;br /&gt;
Of being abandoned, having no one near&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would you lie to me?&lt;br /&gt;
Saying you want me close&lt;br /&gt;
Even though you don’t mean it&lt;br /&gt;
I just needed&lt;br /&gt;
to hear&lt;br /&gt;
someone says it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>A sense of belonging</title>
   <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/a-sense-of-belonging/"/>
   <updated>2021-12-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/a-sense-of=belonging</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The holidays are around the corner… of course I feel sad. I know that I can video call my family in VN, but I still miss the feeling of having a family by my side, a sense of belonging with my beloved in person, I guess. I thought of going back to ATL, but I don’t feel very welcomed just thinking about it; I guess I deserve more than that. Having a friend to keep me in check is great, which prevented me from jumping voluntarily into a potential dumpster fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A sense of belonging, being understood of where I’m coming from, where I’m heading towards and being loved for that. Wouldn’t that be wonderful? Feels good to be able to put it into words (finally? partially? I don’t know, I’m happy with this.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will be the first time I spend all Thanksgiving, Christmas, and New Year by myself. I am pretty sure I do not feel this way when I am in VN around this time of year; probably, the atmosphere and the holiday spirit are differently appreciated here. No more AZ, no more GA. I looked up tickets to Taylor’s comedy shows, which returned a very pricey journey to NY, which I would not want to go by myself. Travels are off. (Ugh?) But let’s think about all the money we’ll save and get to spend somewhere else… Being a broke-ass international phd student in the midst of a pandemic sucks. I’m not gonna lie. I occasionally take pride in the fact that I made it this far. That journey entails tons of hardship. I can name one of them right now - isolation. The path you take, the choices (mistakes) you make, lead you to whatever hellhole you’re in now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In another optimistic news, I’m just so happy to find out about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thriftbooks.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;thriftbooks&lt;/a&gt;. I don’t feel like I have to scroll forever to find a cheap version of a book I wanted to read. Don’t get me wrong, I love the convenience of ebook, with highlighting and looking up terms and whatnot. But the feeling of holding a physical book in your hands, the sound of a highlighter gently moving on the rusty paper, just hit differently.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Do I do stuff, even...</title>
   <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/stuff/"/>
   <updated>2021-12-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/stuff</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Yup. I guess I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎶&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I play the ukulele, baritone ukulele and a little bit guitar, and I like to sing along. I have this little place on
soundcloud for all my
random moments:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/huyendoesstuff/&quot;&gt;https://soundcloud.com/huyendoesstuff/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first I just put it all there, to save the moments for &lt;em&gt;me&lt;/em&gt;. But later, there was this friend of mine who said to
me that she actually liked these audios. And listening to them… means something to her. It
warms my heart just thinking about that :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;✍🏼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ah yes, this blog…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No doubts that I like writing – The reason for the existence of this very page. Most importantly, how to put one
word after one another that closely reflect how I feel – That’s the beauty of the whole thing, learning to express
myself, and also learning about myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📸&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes I take pictures here and there &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/huyendoesstuff/&quot;&gt;https://www.instagram.com/huyendoesstuff/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… Onto the professional stuff:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💻&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am currently a PhD candidate in Computer Science, doing research in Data Visualization. So basically I code and
make visualizations that reveal what data is trying to express.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My public code is at github: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/huyen-nguyen&quot;&gt;https://github.com/huyen-nguyen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📝&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Um and I write manucripts - as a big part of research work. But this a is different kind of writing, which involves
less spontaneity and more rigorous methodology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My publication page: &lt;a href=&quot;https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=tsrO-ZgAAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en&quot;&gt;https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=tsrO-ZgAAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;👩🏻‍🏫&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… and lastly, my &lt;em&gt;very professional&lt;/em&gt; site: &lt;a href=&quot;https://huyennguyen.com&quot;&gt;huyennguyen.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>My books</title>
   <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/my-books/"/>
   <updated>2021-10-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/my-books</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;style type=&quot;text/css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;&gt;
@import url('/assets/css/books.css');
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a very recent reader of books, here is my little collection, in the order that I read:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;side&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;1. &lt;b&gt;No Hard Feelings&lt;/b&gt;: The Secret Power of Embracing Emotions at Work,
     by Liz Fosslien, Mollie West Duffy&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Keywords&lt;/i&gt;: Quotes and stories.&lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;middle&quot;&gt;
  3/10
    &lt;div class=&quot;bar-container&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;bar-30&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/NHFcover.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
  	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/NHFcontent.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;side&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
    	2. &lt;b&gt;The Four Agreements&lt;/b&gt;: A Practical Guide to Personal Freedom (A Toltec Wisdom Book), by don Miguel Ruiz
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Keywords&lt;/i&gt;: Spirituality, extreme opinions, self awareness, love.&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;middle&quot;&gt;
  8/10
    &lt;div class=&quot;bar-container&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;bar-80&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

 &lt;!-- images --&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/TFAcover.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/TFAcontent1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/TFAcontent2.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
  		&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/TFAcontent3.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
  		&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/TFAcontent4.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
			&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/TFAcontent5.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;side&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;3. &lt;b&gt;The Missing Piece Meets The BIG O&lt;/b&gt;, by Shel Silverstein
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;Keywords&lt;/i&gt;: Proactive self improvement, self acceptance.&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;middle&quot;&gt;
 	9/10
    &lt;div class=&quot;bar-container&quot;&gt;
      &lt;div class=&quot;bar-90&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
  	&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/TMPBOcover.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/TMPBOcontent1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
  	&lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
  		&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/TMPBOcontent2.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
  		&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/TMPBOcontent3.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
  	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;myModal&quot; class=&quot;modal&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;modal-content&quot; id=&quot;img01&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div id=&quot;caption&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;/assets/js/d3.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;/assets/js/modal.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>It's been a while</title>
   <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/a-while/"/>
   <updated>2021-10-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/a-while</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh, hello, you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since the last time I was here. Oh, it’s exactly 9 months: January 12 and October 12.
Interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One new thing I learn since the last time I was here is that I need to build the site with &lt;code&gt;jekyll build&lt;/code&gt;, then take only
whatever within the _site folder and put them in the branch for deploying. I was doing it all wrong—no wonder why
it didn’t work as I expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I moved back to the US. Things have been crazy in the last four months. So many things happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I teach now, so I guess I’m a teacher?! Still feel very fresh in the role. I’m truly happy I got to do what I love,
and I love what I do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I know now is that we learn better by &lt;strong&gt;example&lt;/strong&gt;. If you never witness a woman lifts a 200-pound weight,
you may not even believe these kinds of thing happen. But it &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; true. You witness it, and you believe that a human
being can do it, and then you believe &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; can do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently got hooked with reddit. I feel like I can be mindful and intentional about the &lt;em&gt;topics&lt;/em&gt; that I want to
see, instead of feeds with overflowing recommended contents or updates of someone whose life may not be of my
interest.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The narrative on moving through life</title>
   <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/the-narrative/"/>
   <updated>2021-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/the-narrative</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It’s been uneasy for me to write this down, but because of the amount of gratitude I
held dearly in my heart for the support I got from these sensational words, I decided to start this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s the &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/radiantbutch/status/1346136160876302337&quot;&gt;tweet&lt;/a&gt; that has changed the game for me:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;here’s to the people who’s trauma did not give them thick skin. the ones who became more sensitive and
  insecure, who cry more easily, who get overwhelmed at small things. i’m so tired of the narrative that trauma makes you tough and untouchable. we’re survivors, not superheroes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;—– jules rylan ✡︎ @radiantbutch · Jan 4, 2021&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was speechless and emotional after reading the statement. I have always been an emotional person. But this hit hard,
and different. For the first time I feel like I’m free from the expectation where &lt;em&gt;I should be ok by now&lt;/em&gt;, now that I understand I don’t
necessarily have to end my story with a forced positive note.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>My series</title>
   <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/top-series/"/>
   <updated>2021-01-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/top-series</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Fleabag&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Hospital Playlist&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Schitt’s Creek&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;New Girl&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Community/Brooklyn 99&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>My movies</title>
   <link href="huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/top-movies/"/>
   <updated>2020-12-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>huyendoesstuff.github.io/posts/top-movies</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;/* Will add more comments to each of the movies later */&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Little women (2019)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;About time&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Brooklyn&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Pride and Prejudice (2005)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Call me by your name&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Chungking Express&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;500 days of Summer&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Before Sunrise&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Before Sunset&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Wild&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
