<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>huyendoesstuff</title>
 <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="/"/>
 <updated>2021-01-13T03:08:14+07:00</updated>
 <id></id>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>The narrative on moving through life</title>
   <link href="/2021/01/12/the-narrative"/>
   <updated>2021-01-12T00:00:00+07:00</updated>
   <id>/2021/01/12/the-narrative</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It’s been uneasy for me to write this down, but because of the amount of gratitude I 
held dearly in my heart for the support I got from these sensational words, I decided to start this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s the &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/radiantbutch/status/1346136160876302337&quot;&gt;tweet&lt;/a&gt; that has changed the game for me:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;here’s to the people who’s trauma did not give them thick skin. the ones who became more sensitive and 
  insecure, who cry more easily, who get overwhelmed at small things. i’m so tired of the narrative that trauma makes you tough and untouchable. we’re survivors, not superheroes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;—– jules rylan ✡︎ @radiantbutch · Jan 4, 2021&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was speechless and emotional after reading the statement. I have always been an emotional person. But this hit hard, 
and different. For the first time I feel like I’m free from the expectation where &lt;em&gt;I should be ok by now&lt;/em&gt;, now that I understand I don’t 
necessarily have to end my story with a forced positive note.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>My top series</title>
   <link href="/2021/01/09/top-series"/>
   <updated>2021-01-09T00:00:00+07:00</updated>
   <id>/2021/01/09/top-series</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Fleabag&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;New girl&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Community/Brooklyn 99&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>My top 10 movies</title>
   <link href="/2020/12/30/top-movies"/>
   <updated>2020-12-30T00:00:00+07:00</updated>
   <id>/2020/12/30/top-movies</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;/* Will add more comments to each of the movies later */&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Little women (2019)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;About time&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Brooklyn&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Pride and Prejudice (2005)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Call me by your name&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Chungking Express&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;500 days of Summer&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Before Sunrise&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Before Sunset&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Wild&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Small town mentality</title>
   <link href="/2020/12/30/small-town-mentality"/>
   <updated>2020-12-30T00:00:00+07:00</updated>
   <id>/2020/12/30/small-town-mentality</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have been thinking about this for a while. I didn’t know the term &lt;em&gt;small town mentality&lt;/em&gt;, I just knew it has to have	
something to do with &lt;em&gt;small town&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frankly, I’m scared for myself of this mentality. I’m scared it would gradually affect me without me knowing it. I 	
force myself to sit in lab meetings and go to Hanoi or somewhere else just to get myself out of familiar mediocrity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, what is that, the small town mentality?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I looked it up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.quora.com/Why-is-the-small-town-mentality-so-toxic/answer/Zack-Grogan&quot;&gt;answer&lt;/a&gt; on Quora	
very well put, which considered the pros and cons of such mentality. I was struck by this line:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;There’s the distinct feeling that the world is dying around you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;1-context&quot;&gt;1. Context&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The final nudge for me to jot this down is the talk I had with my older cousin earlier this	
evening. She has this reality right in front of her: Unmarried, 30, constantly saying she’s not always this	
depressed, getting upset by upsetting her parents by not married by 30. What happened to her? She hasn’t been able to	
 find a decent man and get married; it now becomes a burden on her and her parents. Like, constantly bang your head against a wall and then realize, “oh, is that a dead-end? Let’s keep hurting ourselves and beat ourselves up for everything bad 	
that happened!” I said to her, age was not a marker of maturity, there was nothing to worry about, and that you can’t 	
control other’s emotions, even if that’s your parents’; you only have the autonomy and control over &lt;strong&gt;your&lt;/strong&gt; life. She did not actively listen at all, 	
wrongly internalize my words, and judged, “When you get older, you will understand. I don’t know who you are if you treat your parents’ sadness like nothing.” I tried to be understanding, but it came to a point where I just couldn’t put up with such nonsense and stupidity.  You can’t 	
really make others happy if you’re not happy, no matter what the excuse of living a shitty life you are telling yourself is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t want to feel sorry for her, but I actually do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t feel sorry for her because of her personality or because of her dwelling in self-pity and self-blame. I feel sorry for her because she let the small town mentality get into her head: The mentality of the scarcity mindset, deep-rooted and growing stronger than ever now that her confidence wears out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;2-its-a-journey-of-realization&quot;&gt;2. It’s a journey of realization&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Different people are on different journeys. Just because this setting is true and meaningful to you, it does not necessarily have to be the same for other people, so have some decency to respect others’ journeys. It’s just that 	
hard, and it’s just that simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a small town, there isn’t much room to deviate from the norm. And once the norm is set to be how patriarchy 	
manifests in both workplace and everyday life, it leads to close-mindedness and gradually dismissing what makes you 	
unique, if it ever exists in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An excerpt of my favorite &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.quora.com/Im-stuck-in-a-small-town-and-my-mentality-is-completely-different-from-the-people-that-live-here-Im-socially-isolated-and-I-have-no-friends-My-family-also-lives-here-but-Im-unhappy-How-do-I-cope-Should-I-live-here/answer/Christopher-Aune&quot;&gt;answer&lt;/a&gt; on Quora:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“First, find your self. It’s easy to lose yourself in your family’s town. You end up trying to be what everybody expects you to be. They can even get angry and downright mean if you stop being what they expect. It messes up their little world. […]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Second, go on travel adventures. Pick out some areas with the type of culture and geography you are attracted to.”	
(I told my cousin to go on some adventures, maybe go out of town for a while to some new city and take your laptop with you to work on the go. But she took it as me diminishing the place she was in “Even if my 	
family lives in some remote, deserted area, it is still my family.” I mean, I can’t even…)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am lucky enough to go out there and learn for myself that the world is full of possibilities: Possibilities to change the world for the better, possibilities to break the deep-rooted prejudice, and possibilities to live happily even though you’re not what everybody expects you to be. I am also fortunate enough to see that people at any age, 	
whether they are in a relationship, a marriage, or in their journey of finding, healing, and loving themselves, can be happy, fulfilled, vulnerable, lost, or sad, or any emotion that may arise. We are learning as we go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Gary Vee: * “I only live on my funeral.”&lt;em&gt;, this leads me to a “big word” 	
that I find myself refrain from using: Legacy. What is the *legacy&lt;/em&gt; I would leave on this earth the day I die?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;3-that-shouldnt-be-just-one-idea-anyway&quot;&gt;3. That shouldn’t be just one idea anyway&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yup, the title of this section is &lt;a href=&quot;https://parksandrecreation.fandom.com/wiki/Ben_Wyatt&quot;&gt;Ben Wyatt&lt;/a&gt; ‘s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The danger of the small town mentality is that, as there is not much room to deviate from the norm, any act of being different are shunned and easily to be considered “frowned upon”, putting pressure on the ones that are just trying to live &lt;strong&gt;their&lt;/strong&gt; life how they wanted to. It makes people petty and close-minded and extremely easy to judge, as there is a big group having the same judgment towards some &lt;em&gt;outcast.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the signs and make way for yourself. Remember, you have full autonomy over your life. No one can do that for 	
you and no one can do that as good as you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will end this post with a lovely, powerful statement from &lt;a href=&quot;https://parksandrecreation.fandom.com/wiki/Leslie_Knope&quot;&gt;Leslie Knope&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you wanna bake a pie, that’s great. If you wanna have a career, that’s great too. Do both, or neither, doesn’t 	
matter, just don’t judge what someone else has decided to do. We’re all just trying to find the right path for us. As individuals. On this earth.	
We’re just some flawed human beings, trying to navigate through life and create the connection along the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
